[Music]
In the name of God, I greet you and have a good time.
Dear friends and companions, we are very happy to be with
you with the new Trident Course of the Zeus Group. This course is published in its entirety in
a dedicated playlist with the same name on the
official Zeus YouTube page at the address Zeus Forex Channel,
and all sessions can be viewed in order from the
first part.  In this course,
you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After
watching each session, you can practice
and then watch 6 short half-hour sessions of
troubleshooting by friends who participated in the round
to get a better understanding of the material.
After that, you will enter the next teaching session.
To communicate directly with us and use the
troubleshooting plans, just
send me a message using the Zeus Group Underline Telegram ID and
stay in touch with us.  Wishing you success in your
trading career, dear.
In the name of God,
Minaret number three, the black cargo ship, has gone.
Hello Mr. Reza, don't be tired.  Good time.
Hello. Good time for you too. Sir. Sincerely. Thank you. Thank you.
I really didn't have any questions. My
only question was, for example, in the
components of an F-Diyar or King,
from which component does the price return? For example, the
ELMPL and then the swaps were these.
I wanted to see from which component the
price returns. Now, I don't know if you want to explain this in the future
or if it's possible now. I'll
tell you something right now. We don't have any other MPL at all.
In the discussion,
yes, I
said, we said it in the D period, but to
avoid using too many words, you have a high origin and a
low origin. That's
right.
In one, we
expect the price to return from the order. This
order is
not exactly at the last point of the
last king or the first point of the king. We decide on it
based on what happened in the king, its
position and its alignment with the
higher time zones.
But in general, in the king,
a left shoulder is important. Another decision is
not important.
Now, that discussion is that if it becomes a juggernaut,
the price will return. Here it is, step by step.  We'll get there,
but in order to clear your mind
of those previous sentences, for example, so that there's
no conflict,
MPL and these are important orders in a king. The most
important thing is to come and
say 50
candles, no 50 candles, no 50 kinks.
The order can be at the end of a king. The order
can be in the middle of a king. You have to look at
how big the king is. Does the
kink itself hold the price? It ca
n't hold. I have to check these. Thank you
very much. Thank you. Please. Please. What
was the previous number? Mr.
Jal asked a question. The number is 26. Yes, yes, yes.
26. You
sent these 14 four exercises. That's right. Yes,
now because I seem to have just registered for these classes
for the first time.
Now, I'll send you the
rest for the first time.
Now, I don't know. Friends, maybe they have experience in
these classes. I don't know. Take
some time now to study the rest.
Leave a journal. But the exercises are not enough. I do
n't know what. What I'm seeing is that there should
n't be too many exercises. There
should be a lot of exercises.  God forbid you will
suffer in the future.
What will help you is to
practice. You
wrote Kink S.
Yes, that was LS.
What does
SLS mean? It's
like the SNR that we were drawing from RS.
Well, tell me.
Yes, the same LS that we were talking about.
This depends on the same RS. You used to say that in the
previous meetings that you came to, you explained.
I said this based on the same LS. In a
few meetings, I said, in the video.
In the previous video, the previous question that I was watching now.
No,
Mr. Behshad. I recorded the video exercises that
you came to this time. This time, I recorded a video
for that group. The videos that we are
watching now are based on that video and according to the
examples in the video.
Send me the exercises. My mind has become one with that.
If you do this, you will be doing yourself a favor.
Yes, yes, it will be
right. God willing, it will be
at
your service in the future meetings. It won't hurt. Thank you. Please, sir. What
was the number of that other case?
Number 31. Mr. Monshirzadeh.
Mr. Monshizadeh is the tenth of
Monshizadeh. I think so.
Hello.  Mr. Reza, how are you?
Hello, how are you? You are a good person.
Monshizade and Monshizade are the same pair. It doesn't matter
which one you are, you are comfortable.
No, well, excuse me if the pronunciation and stuff are
not okay. I apologize a little. I
was busy with something. My number of exercises is small. I had a problem. I
mean, I wasn't paying attention
during the exercise. This confirmation in King Swap was
also confirmed. I drew the problem I had.
Now the admin told me that. I understood it. Now
look at my journal again. If there is a problem, tell me. I
learned the RT from someone else. It was
very different. That's why I'm
clearing my mind and focusing on what you are
explaining. The truth is,
I had never heard of these terms, such as
King
Swap and these, before. I
mean, I didn't know what they taught us.
Now draw a flag, a new flag, a
DP, and then come to MPL in DP and I
don't know if we should
find a price and trade on MPL or on
MPL. We all ended up losing money.
The truth is, with seven eights, for example,
you are
in your training now, kings, kinks, no, king, king,
becomes king, kink, king, kin,
yes, this is in, yes, it's wrong,
because I had taken a screenshot, I do
n't remember or not, now the word is not very important to us,
but now, for example, later, why do you draw
these in reverse,
where do you swap, for example, practice, for example,
let me get a copy,
eyes
here
[music],
for example, here
and now you took this kink, this news, this
swap is red, you
took it out of this,
look out, king,
after the broken stanari, I drew it correctly,
see, this is what happens,
soups,
soup, this blue, don't you want to draw it? Yes, it
means from the foot, because it broke from the bottom, from the low, I
have to take it from the low to the retracement that came back. That's right, yes,
we said this. Think about it, you
have a king here. A:
Here was a king, it was blue. The
price came in the future, this is going down. When the
retracement gave,
yes,
then this low passed this low, this low means this
retracement this low.  It crossed here, you are the
box range. Now this box range has gone down and has
come back again. Re-
confirmed. Now,
no, it has been swapped again. That is, it has come back once.
Now, I don't want to swap like this.
Remember, I mean, this can be a box.
This can be a box range.
Now, I have a question. Kink Kink Blue on me, which
happened after the breakout. Right. Right. Yes, well,
this has kept the price up. Right.
King
kept it up. He couldn't react
to the price coming from over there. He
couldn't react at all. Oh, okay.
This confirmation is the same green candle
that has a small shadow. Right.
Kink confirmation after the breakout.
Look, it's confirmed for blue here. Yes, yes,
for blue here.
For red here. It's confirmed here.
Here, for
its boxes. I understood what it was. It was drawn the opposite way.
Yes, I'll put this in your advertisement.
Now, try to correct these. We
told you here. But, experts,
ask me anything you have a problem with. Now, you
drew the top right
before the breakout. You drew it right. But again, here, I
feel like you're saying a
block order. I've worked before.
City RT M Yes, we worked together. Well,
I'm one of my friends. That's why
I'm confused now in the failures. I have to
draw the right order on the failures.
Now
look at what you drew.
What is your first name?
Enshzadeh
went hard. I got
sick. I think he hit him.
Well,
this looks like an order block.
[Music] The
next person is now cut off.
Shahabi.
When did you say two people came? D to D to D
accounts.
Now you have one account. Mr. Pouya,
number 32. Mr. Shahabi Ashkan.
Hello. Good time. God. Hello. Don't be tired.
Shabi. Good time. I do
n't have any specific questions. Mr. Reza Pirouz. What you just
said in the discussion is now the orders inside
the one.
Is it possible that now in
Skyla or lower time frames, we can have,
for example, orders inside the one. And
if possible, can we
filter these orders and know exactly from
which one they come?  You have to
work with probabilities,
you know, except for, look, no, I have no
certainty about anything in the market. The
market is very flexible with respect to events. But it shows
us a series of things. It shows us a
series of paths. Based on those
paths, we know that this week it will go down,
that week it will go up, for example, during the week. We also make
mistakes somewhere. It's not that
accurate. For example, let's say here,
yes, we make a lot of pips. We do it
in the eyes of everyone, but we don't make a lot of money.
This is a rule for traders. No,
we all do this. Anyone who comes into this
market, well, that's it. But what I'm
saying, for example, is that we consider a range in a chart
or in one that we consider.
This range is based on what events
occur on the chart. For example, we say that
this range is good for buys. This range is the
result of a drop. What did this drop do?
For example, it created a view. Well,
in this curve, if it is much larger, it is
smaller.  But if, for example, the time frame
is one minute, now to avoid getting confused, you can
trade its edges. For
example, you don't want to search for a range of 10 pips or 15 pips
anymore because it may
come and not activate your order.
But we know that the higher the time frame, the
greater the value of that range or that kink,
and we make decisions based on that.
Now, for example, we learned what a
king ancestor is. We made the upper and lower limits of the king.
But later we will also learn that, for example, for example, a
king can be a priority if its own board is violated.
Many of these cases are
not useful below it. The one above, for example, that kink
above it is useful. We will learn this,
but
with the opposite pi, not with another pi,
when it is not under one, it is open.
At all, whatever you take, this will come and go
below this,
but yes, the
range that it has now
for
trading or ordering.  Pay attention to
the reading that is done in the king, for example,
you say this as a king, say from
this lu to this hand, when it is not useful, it does
not hold. For example, I tell you,
take this king, where is this kink?
This has no ability to hold the price even here with the
price of these, there is a
reason because, for example,
the lu itself is broken, it cannot hold these, we
need to add my help to it, that is,
after conditions such as the self-correction of the
king itself, it has eaten in the right place, now depending
on that right place, I will post
and these, yes, then I will put a few shields inside the king,
so
see, when the king is formed, that is,
here the kings, when it is formed, it
goes up,
well, maybe before leaving this king, that is,
before here, before the king is
confirmed and the price comes out of it, maybe after
a million hits, you expect the
price to come down on this order, but on the
way it is ignoring an area or there is
a left in this, it is hitting this.  The area
and in the future after this hio breaks and
goes to open a pazio from above, do it back
to this because this is in line
with this order,
there is an order that now when it is confirmed by the king,
that range can work, in the future
this golf, that ingolfam finally
has a reaction, a low and small time frame
here, for example, one, but an order
that makes sense in the time structure and shows the violation,
this is the top, when it goes to hit it, it is small, small, small, small,
finally, everywhere the price
goes to a kink, it returns to a kink, if
we want to be small like this again, we will
not understand where this golf, where this golf
is not, it is better to learn now that an order
in a
time structure area, when it goes below it, it
becomes ingolfam, but the price goes to a
lower time frame,
which is what
this trading is doing now, Abbasineh,
dad, this is absolutely, for
God's sake, send it to him right now, send it to Amir Hossein,
send it to this
d-to the topic now  One is a topic that
was in the second period, we heard that it was not recorded, the
KHP topic, and the other is the
price manipulation topic that you mentioned. Now, if you think it is
useful to us, please
tell us what the
hell the men call it.
We abbreviated it, so it becomes Ketchup. Now,
what was the topic that you mentioned? The
price manipulation topic is a
video of me that we discussed in the discussion session. He
talks about it in the index.
Yes, thank you
very much.
Please be healthy.  So, you came
here.
So
this is
your practice, right?
Yes, yes, yes,
what logic did you use to pull this stunt
?
[Music]
Look at the black candle after the green one, which
retraced down, there was
nothing left to go, it wasn't
confirmed at all, because it was in the middle, how should I
say, why was it confirmed? Right, for a moment I
was confused, I don't know which exercise I was doing.
Look, I'll tell you, this king does
n't exist at all, because
this king must be the result of this failure.
This FT goes here. This king is
this FT. Now, regarding these
things that exist here, I'm
telling you, regarding these things that are here, this FT that you
took before the failure and because it went here and
crossed this line above it, there was no failure in the middle.
Then the price came and ate here, it
gave a reaction.
Yes,
hello, okay, now
we corrected this there, but what I mean is, pay
attention a little bit now. This slide is the same one
I wanted to see because I'm saying, for a moment, I
want to work on my empty RT again, and
just move forward with your own style. Let's, for
example, send exercises from previous sessions
in our journal so that I can
relax. Now, for example, session one and 100.  For
example, I'm OK now, I'm OK now, I'm just a little bit confused about the kinks
before the break and then the break and on the break now on the
break I'm OK now, I'm having trouble with the breaks after the breaks
no problem you can send it in a week later
but well, for example yes it was approved let's go to the
meeting let's go to the next meetings B
a question king
kink so should it always be bigger than the previous kink
that comes from the kink structure that comes it should
be bigger no no
now you
look at the page
yes we have a king for example
here you have a king that is the result of the break of this low
right the result of the break of this low yes yes more
to draw the swap it is enough for the price to break this upper edge
means this upper edge the price will
break
then give a retracement to confirm this edge
if you go ahead the first one broke the second one
broke the second one broke yes
and it was confirmed and held again so this is
king
soup these
yes then yes yes I understand now I
don't know if this question has anything to do with us at all
we always had a problem when I came I learned artio in general we don't know we did
n't know exactly where to put the
point  Let's enter and for example
how to define the target. We will understand this completely in the next sessions.
Look, we have two or three examples, two definitions
for our target. The rest is just repetition.
One is the left shoulders, that
is, the left shoulders as the target.
The second is the decisions of the target itself. The target itself can be this golf.
The target itself can be this golf.
This is a different discussion.
Well, my problem was always that I did
n't know where to
enter. For example, we found the components of Kingo. We found
everything. We did PL and DP.
Now that we don't have them anymore, I think you said, or
now, for example, it
moves forward based on the materials that are said and now a new structure, a
mental structure. Now, where the vag was, it will help me. It will take
four or five sessions.
So compare these. I think
I should practice more than the others
because a little bit.
Yes, this is Kane. Yes, okay.
I will send you the exercises of session
one. Now, as far as you can see, it's okay.
Tell me I won't send it. Okay, thank you
very much.
Please, next person.
[Music]
He.
เ